<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Quang Nguyen - book</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/book.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2018-08-22T11:11:42+00:00</updated><entry><title>Part III - Deep Learning</title><link href="/blog/book/2018/part-3-deep-learning/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-08-22T11:11:42+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-22T11:11:42+00:00</updated><author><name>Quang Nguyen</name></author><id>tag:None,2018-08-22:/blog/book/2018/part-3-deep-learning/</id><summary type="html">&lt;h1 id="part-iii"&gt;Part III&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This part of the book describes the more ambitious and advanced approaches to deep learning, currently pursued by the research community. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the previous parts of the book, we have shown how to solve supervised learning problems - how to map one vector to another given enough examples of the mapping. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not all problems we might want to solve fall into this category. We may wish to generate new examples, or determine how likely some point is, or handle missing values and take advantage of a large set of unlabeled examples or examples from related tasks. A shortcoming of the current state of the art for industrial applications is that our learning algorithms require large amounts of supervised data to achieve good accuracy. In this part of the book, we discuss some of the speculative approaches to reducing the amount of labeled data necessary for existing models to work …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h1 id="part-iii"&gt;Part III&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This part of the book describes the more ambitious and advanced approaches to deep learning, currently pursued by the research community. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the previous parts of the book, we have shown how to solve supervised learning problems - how to map one vector to another given enough examples of the mapping. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not all problems we might want to solve fall into this category. We may wish to generate new examples, or determine how likely some point is, or handle missing values and take advantage of a large set of unlabeled examples or examples from related tasks. A shortcoming of the current state of the art for industrial applications is that our learning algorithms require large amounts of supervised data to achieve good accuracy. In this part of the book, we discuss some of the speculative approaches to reducing the amount of labeled data necessary for existing models to work well and be applicable across a broader range of tasks. Accomplishing these goals usually requires some form of unsupervised or semi-supervised learning. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many deep learning algorithms have been designed to tackle un&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Deep Learning"></category><category term="BOOK"></category></entry></feed>